A Finding Aid to the American Federation of Arts Records, 1895-1993 (bulk 1909-1969), in the Archives of American Art AAA.amerfeda
Archives of American Art
Calcagno, Lawrence: 56-1, 56-12, 60-22, 61-29, ME-33, ME-42, ME-49
Calder, Alexander: 60-42, 62-1, 64-10, ME-10, ME-32, NY-20
Calderani & Franscassini, Virgilio & Renzo: 61-1
Caliga, Elizabeth Howland: 64-30
Caliga, I.H.: 64-29, 64-30
Callahan: NY-20
Callahan, Harry M.: 57-25, 59-56, 63-8
Callahan, Kenneth: 55-21, 56-1, 57-1, 57-10, 58-42, 58-43, 61-15, 62-29, 65-11, ME-73, ME-75
Callister, Charles Warren: 64-21
Callot, Jacques: 55-24, 57-37, 59-20, 63-17, NY-9
Callow, John: 62-12
Callow, William: 67-19
Calpp, A1: 57-3
Camaro, Alexander: NE-48
Cambellotti, Laura: 61-1
Cambiasco, Luca: 62-20, 64-9, ME-32
Cameron, David Young (Sir): 62-45
Cameron, Julia Margaret: 56-5, 62-25, NY-1
Campagnola Domenico: 55-24
Campbell, Gretna: 56-2
Campbell, J. Todd: 62-10
Campbell, Jerry Ray: 62-10
Campbell, Lawrence: 55-3
Campbell, Paschall: 62-33
Campbell, Peter: 64-28
Campendonk, Heinrich: 62-29
Campigli, Massimo: 51-18, 55-13, 57-34, 58-23, 61-16
Campoli, Cosmo: 56-12
Campos, Manuel Lalorre: 61-1
Canaletto: 61-22, 64-6, 67-19
Candell, Victor: 56-1, 56-2, 57-10, 60-1, 64-29, 64-30, ME-73
Candellahan, Victor: 56-1
Caniff, Milton: 57-3
Canna, Pasquale: 58-9
Cano, Alonso: 62-20
Canogar, Rafael: 64-2
Canova, Antonio: ME-32
Cantagallina, Remigio: 59-40
Cantarini, Simone: 64-6
Cantatore: 51-18
Cantu, Frederico: 54-16
Capa, Cornell: 58-A&B, 59-56
Capa ,Robert: 58-A&B, 59-56
Caparn, Rhys: 52-4, 62-40, ME-56
Capehart, Noyes: 64-7
Capogrossi, Giuseppe: 54-18, 58-23, 61-16, 59-35
Cappelli, Giovanni: 58-40
Capraro, Vincent: 58-40
Capuletti: 59-19
Caraglio, Jacopo: 62-18
Cardwell, Don: 51-15
Carey, J. Sheldon: 60-5
Cargill, David: 58-30
Cariola, Robert: ME-75
Carl Koch & Associates, Inc.: 63-16
Carle, Roger: 59-5
Carles, Arthur B.: 57-9, 63-3, ME-55
Carlin, Earl P.: 62-24
Carlin, James: 53-1
Carlsen, Emil: 56-18
Carmassi, Arturo: 59-35, 60-20
Carmi, T.: 58-36
Caro, Anthony: 61-2
Carone, Nicholas: 57-9, 59-23, 61-29, 62-37, ME-33, ME-42
Carot, Camille: 63-20
Carpenter, Arthur Espenet: 57-6, 64-23
Carpi, Girolamo da: 62-20
Carra, Carlo: 57-34, 58-23
Carracci, Agostino: 64-6
Carracci, Annibale: 64-6
Carracci, Lodovico: 62-20
Carreno, Mario: 56-28, 62-6
Carriere, Eugene: 62-5
Carroll, Jo: 55-20
Carroll, John: 62-30
Carroll, & Daeuble: ME-19
Carter, Caleb: 63-15
Carter, John A.: 59-12
Carter, John Clay: 53-26
Cartier-Bresson, Henri: 56-5, 57-39, 59-56, 60-25
Cartwright, Roy: 62-10
Caruso, Bruno: 55-7, 58-15
Caruso, Nino: 61-1
Caruthers, John: 58-32
Carwitham, I.: ME-29
Carzou, Jean: 56-15, 58-15
Casarella, Edmund: 53-16, 55-2, 55-20, 56-25, 56-26, 58-3, 60-3, 60-15, 60-22, 60-24, 62-3, 64-7, NY-3
Casebier, Cecil Lang: 55-2, 56-12, 57-1, 57-23
Casilear, John William: 60-28, 64-3
Casinari, Bruno: 58-23
Casolani, Alessandro di Agostino: 64-9
Casorati, Felice: 51-18, 58-23
Casrella Edmond: 56-26, 57-12
Cassara, Frank: 60-3
Cassatt, Mary: 54-25, 60-13, 62-45, 61-1, ME-7, ME-31, ME-41, MMA-54-1
Cassidy, Gertrude (Dr): 58-35
Cassill, H.C.: 55-20, 56-26, 60-3, 62-3
Cassill, Jean Kubota: 55-20
Cassinari: 51-18
Cassinari, Bruno: 61-16
Castel, Moshe: 54-27
Castellón, Federico: 53-2, 56-26, 62-1, 62-18, 64-7, ME-7
Castiglione, Giovani Benedetto: 59-40, 64-6, 67-19
Catena, Vincenzo: 64-19
Cathelin, Bernard: 63-14
Cathrineholm, A.S.: 57-40
Catich, E.M. (Father): 58-16
Catlin, George: 59-18, 61-3, ME-11, ME-29
Caudill, Rowlett & Scott: ME-19
Causo, Bruno: 54-27
Cavaglieri, Georgio: 61-30
Cavailles, Jr.: 59-5
Cavallito, Albino: 52-4
Cavanaugh, John: 62-40, ME-56
Cazin, Jean Charles: MMA-54-4
Ceare, Oscar: 57-3
Cecioni, Adriano: 63-10
Celic, Stojan: 59-16
Center, J.C.: 64-3
Cernigoj, August: 56-21
Cerny, Geiorge: 52-4
Cerra, Mirta: 56-28
Cesari, Giuseep: 59-40
Cézanne, Paul: 55-24, 57-18, 62-5, 63-14, NY-7&7b
Ch'en, Ch'I Kaun: 58-42
Chabba, A.: 58-36
Chadel, Jules: 54-16
Chadwick, Gordon: 64-21
Chadwick, Lynn: 60-14, 63-31
Chae-hyo, Song: 58-33
Chaet, Bernard: 62-3, 65-11
Chafetz, Sidney: 56-2, 56-25
Chaffee, Oliver Newberry: 64-30
Chagall, Marc: 54-16, 54-18, 56-15, 58-15, 60-14, 60-15, 60-44, 61-16, 62-29, 63-14, ME-65
Chailleat, Leonard: 59-40
Chait, Daniel: 62-34
Chamberlain, John: 63-29
Chamberlain, Samuel: 59-6
Chambers, Thomas: 62-2, ME-11
Chambers, William (Sir): 61-22
Chament, Guiuseppe: 58-9
Champney, Benjamin: NY-4
Champney, James Wells: 64-1
Chandler, Winthrop: 62-2
Chandler, Christy Howard: 57-17
Chapallaz, Edouard: 61-1
Chapin, David: 61-23
Chapin, Francis: 53-5, 64-30, ME-7
Chapin, James: 64-3
Chapin, Mary S.: 64-1
Chapman, Charles S.: 64-3
Chapman, John G.: 58-27
Chappell, Walter: 60-12, 61-13
Chappell, William: 59-19
Charag-Zunz, C.: 58-36
Chardin, Jean-Baptiste Simeon: 56-16
Charles, M. Goodman Assoc: 58-1
Charlot, Jean: 53-1, NE-96
Charpin, Francis: 56-19
Chase, Barbara: 66-9
Chase, William Merritt: 56-18, 59-6, 59-34, 62-7, 62-17, 63-3, 64-3, ME-7
Chavez, Edward Arcenio: 55-5, 57-1, 57-10
Chayat, Maxwell M.: 61-17, ME-75
Cheever, Abbott: 59-6
Chen, Chi: 55-2, 55-19, 55-21, 64-19, ME-65, ME-73
Chenoweth, Mary: 58-3
Cherner, Norman: 61-30
Cherney, Marvin: 62-31
Cherry, Couise: 55-22
Chesney, Lee: 53-5, 53-16, 55-20, 56-12, 56-25, 56-26, 58-3, 60-3, 60-22
Chey, Katharine: 57-6
Chiarottini, Francesco: 58-9
Chieffo, Clifford T.: 65-4
Chighine, Alfredo: 58-23
Child, Anne: 60-41
Childs, Bernard: 58-42
Chillida, Eduardo: 61-4, 62-29, 64-10
Chinnery George: 67-19
Chippendale, Thomas: 59-40
Chow, Fong: 57-6
Choy, Katherine: 57-14
Christ, Rudolf: 53-21
Christensen, Hans: 57-6, 60-5
Christiana, Mike: 60-3, NY-3
Christopher William: 63-7, 65-4
Christus, Petrus: 56-16
Christy, Howard Chandler: 59-6
Chruchward, L.: 58-32
Chryssa, V.: 62-40, ME-56
Chudo, Ken'ichi: 65-12
Chumly, John W.: 58-39
Church, Frederick Edwin: 59-34, 59-40, 60-28, ME-11NY-4
Ciampi, Mario J.: 62-34
Ciceri: 63-19
Cicero, Carmen: 56-12, ME-73, NY-10
Cikovsky, Nicolai: 57-10, ME-73
Cimiotti Emil: 61-4
Ciry, Michael: 54-16, 58-15, 60-15
Citroen, Paul: 53-2
Citron, Minna: 53-5, 53-16, 56-2, 56-25, 57-32 58-3, 58-26, 60-24, 62-8, 64-30, 57-36
Claret, Juan: 64-17
Clark, Carolyn J.: 53-26
Clark, Edward: 58-A&B
Clark, Ester: 62-10
Clark, J. & C.: NY-15
Clark & Beuttler, Hervey Parke & John F.: 64-11
Clarke, Arundel: 62-15
Clarke, Geoffrey: 54-18
Clarke & Beuttler, Hevey Parke & John F.: SD-8
Clarke & Rapuano: 62-33
Claudet: 56-5
Clave, Antonio: 54-16, 56-15, 58-15, 59-19, 64-17, NE-96
Clement, Marita van der Poest: 62-8
Clements, Thomas: 58-39
Clerisseau, Charles: 62-20
Cliffe, Henry: 54-18, 60-15
Cloar, Carroll: 58-44, 61-35, 64-4, 65-2, ME-73
Clonney, James Goodwyn: 64-1
Clough, Ebenezer: NY-14
Clough, Prunella: NE-96
Clove: 59-5
Clutz, William: 60-43, NY-18
Clymer, J. Floyd: 64-30
Coat, Pierre Tal: 61-4
Cobb, Ruth: 53-5, 64-30
Cobbaert, Jan: 61-1
Cobean, Sam: 55-13, ME-28
Coburn, Alvin Langdon: 56-5, 62-25, 64-28, NY-1
Cochran, Donald: 58-39
Cocke, Bartlett: ME-19
Cocke, Bowman & Yorke: ME-19
Cockerell, Charles Robert: 61-22
Cocteau, Jean: 56-15
Coecke, van Aelst Pieter: 64-9
Coen, Eleanor: 53-1, 54-18, 55-20, 56-15, 56-19, 56-25, 56-26, 59-10, 62-3, NE-96
Coffey, Clara Stimson: 62-33
Coggeshall, Calvert: ME-59
Cohen, George: 59-12
Cohen, John: 59-12
Cohen, Michael: 58-32, 62-10
Cohen, Roda: 58-3
Cohen, Wdilfred P.: 57-ee
Coke, Van Deren: 60-12
Colby, Frederick L.: 57-6
Cole, Thomas: 59-24, 59-34, 60-28, 64-1, 65-10, ME-11, NY-4
Cole-Ruddick, Dorothy: 52-7
Coleman, John: 62-3, 64-7
Coleman, Muriel: 52-7
Colescott, Warrington: 53-16, 55-20, 56-2, 58-3, 62-3
Colgren, Monte L.: 58-32
Colker, Edward: 56-12
Collaert, Hans: 63-9
Collins, Alfred Quinton: 62-7
Collins, Arnold: NY-13
Collins, Lowell: 57-23
Colman, Samuel: 59-6, 60-28, 64-1
Colombino, Carlos: 60-17
Colquhoun, Robert: 54-18, NE-96
Colton, Paula: 58-32
Colville, Alex: 55-19, 59-3, NY-17
Colvin, Franklin: 58-25
Comegys, George H.: 58-14
Commins, Terrell D.: 53-17
Comtant: 51-3
Conca, Sebastiano: 62-20, 62-36
Conder, Charles: 62-12
Congdon, William: 60-22, 64-19, ME-59, ME-65, ME-75
Coninxloo: 54-11
Conkey, George: 53-26
Connah, Whit: 61-35, 65-11
Connaway, Jay Hall: 62-17, 64-31
Connelly, Brian: 64-4
Conner, Charles: 58-27
Connor, Russell: 56-27
Conover, Robert F.: 53-16, 55-20, 56-25, 56-26, 57-12, 58-3, 60-3, 60-15, 60-24, 62-3, 64-7, NY-3
Consagra, Pietro: 60-2, 61-11, 62-40, 63-31, ME-56
Constable, John: 56-16, 57-18, 62-12, 62-20, 63-20, 67-19
Constan,t George: 55-3, 56-2, 56-25, ME-26, ME-73
Consuegra, Hugo: 56-28
Conway, Fred: 51-5, 53-12, 56-2, ME-73
Cook: 63-19
Cook, Christopher: 65-11
Cook, Donald: 59-6
Cook, Edward A.: 53-17
Cook, Gordon: 56-25, 60-3
Cook, Howard Norton: ME-7
Cooke, Betty: 53-24
Cooke, Jerry: 59-56
Coonley, John C.: 53-24
Cooper, Mario: 53-8
Cooper, T.S.: 64-5
Coornhert, Dirk Volkertsz: 62-18
Copeland, Lawrence G.: 57-6
Copeland, Novak & Israel: 61-30
Copello, Franesco: ME-75
Copley: 54-25
Copley, John Singleton: 54-25, 60-13, 62-17, 62-20, 63-15, ME-7, ME-31, ME-32, ME-41
Corbett, Edward: ME-73
Corbett, Mario: SD-8
Corbin, Lock Company: NY-15
Corbino, Jon: 53-12, 55-19
Corbridge, Edgar: 64-30
Corinth, Lovis: 61-25, 63-17
Corita, Mary (Sister): 53-5, 53-16, 56-25, 58-16, 58-35, 60-3
Corneille: 58-29, 61-29, 64-2
Cornell, Joseph: 59-14
Cornell, Thomas: 60-3, 64-25
Coronel, Raul A.: 55-22, 57-14
Corot, Jean Baptiste Camille: 56-16, 63-17, 65-10, ME-32, MMA-54-4
Corpora, Antonio: 58-15, 58-23, 61-16
Corsaw Roger D.: 60-5
Corson, David T.: 55-2
Cortlandt, Lyn: 58-3
Cortlandt, Zulema: 58-3
Cortona, Pietro da: 62-20
Cosijn, Lies: 61-1
Costa, Giovanni: 63-10
Costigan, John: 63-33
Cote, Alan: 58-39
Cotman, John Sell: 61-22, 62-12
Couch, Rebecca: 59-18
Couch, Urban: 58-6, 65-7
Coughtry, Graham: 58-6
Coulentianos, Costa: 54-18
Coulter, Dorothy: 65-11
Countey, Edward: 60-3
Courbet, Gustave: 63-14, 63-20, 65-10, ME-55, MMA-54-2, MMA-54-4
Courtin, Pierre Tal: 61-11
Covert, John: 55-15
Covington, Harrison: 54-42, 61-35
Cowles, Hobart E.: 57-6
Cowles, Russell: 53-5, 56-19
Cowley, Edward: 54-27
Cox, David: 62-12
Cox, Jan: 56-15, NE-96
Cox, John Rogers: NY-7&7b
Cox, Joseph: 61-35
Cox, Kenyon: 59-6, 62-7
Cox Palmer: 59-6
Cozzens, Frederick S.: 64-3
Cozzi, Ciriaco: 55-5
Crafts, Lemurian: 57-6
Craig: 63-19
Craig Ellwood Assoc: 62-34
Craighead, Charlene: 62-3
Cramer, Jaray & Paillard: 53-21
Crampton, Rollin: 62-37, 64-26
Cranach, Lucas (the Elder): 56-16, 57-18, 57-37, 62-27, ME-55, NY-9
Crane: 57-3
Crane, Ralph: 58-A&B
Crane, Roy: 57-3
Crane, Walter: 63-5
Cranmer, Jr., Thomas E.: 58-3
Cranstone, Lefevre James: 64-1
Crates, James: 65-7
Craven, Jr., Roy C.: 56-9, 61-35
Crawford, Ralston: 53-5, 53-9, 53-12, 54-18, 55-13, 56-15, 57-28, 58-15, 58-44, 60-22, 61-25, ME-73, NE-96, NY-20
Craxton, John: 59-19
Creative Playthings: 65-6
Cremean, Robert: 60-2
Cremonini, Leonardo: 54-16, 57-34, 61-4, 62-28, 64-2
Cress, George: 54-8
Cressey, David: 64-23
Cressey, Donna: 58-32
Crippa, Roberto: 56-19
Cristiano, Renato: 57-27
Crite, Allan R.: 59-6
Crome, John: 65-10
Cronbach, Robert: 52-4, 65-3, ME-75
Cropsey, Jasper Francis: 59-6, 60-28, 64-1, 64-3, ME-11, NY-4
Cross, Henri E.: 62-5
Crossgrove, Roger: ME-74
Crouwel, Wim: 61-20
Crozier, William Tylee: 61-4
Crumrine, James: 63-5
Cruz, Emilio: 66-9
Csoka, Stephen: 58-16
Cuevas, José Luis: 56-15, 63-12, ME-45
Culverhouse, Johann Mongels: 55-19
Culwell, Ben: 57-23, 57-ee
Cummings, Thomas Seir: 58-14
Cunningham, Ben: 52-11
Cunningham, Hester: 62-15
Cunningham, Imogen: 56-5
Cuomo, Sylvia: 57-14
Curmrine, James: 57-6
Currie, Bruce: 56-13
Currier, J. Frank: 64-3
Currier, N.: ME-29
Currier & Ives: ME-29
Curry, John Steuart: 54-25, 55-16, 60-13, ME-31
Curtis, E.L.: 54-12
Curtis & Davis: 62-34
Cushing, Lily: 55-21
Cushing, Otho: 57-3
Cushing, Val: 57-14, 58-32, 59-12
Cusumano, Stefano: ME-73
Cuyp: 54-11
Cyren, Gunnar: 57-14
Cyril: 62-8
Czaja, Michael: VA-53-1
Czermanski, Zdzislaw: 55-13
Czuri, Charles A.: 57-10
D'Ancona, Vito: 63-10
D'Arista, Robert: 55-9
D'Arte, Seguso Vetri: 61-1
D'Haese, Roel: 61-4
D'Orazio, Piero: 58-23
D'Orgeix, Christian: 61-4
da Carpi, Girolamo: 59-40
da Cortona, Pietro Berrettini: 61-22
Da Fabriano, Gentile: 56-16
da Sangallo, Francesco: 59-40
da Silva, Maria Helena Vieira: 60-14
da Silva, Vieira: 62-28, ME-40
da Silveira, Elisa Martins: 60-17
da Vinci, Leonardo: 53-3, 57-18, 64-9
da Volterra, Daniele: 55-24
Dahemers, Robert: 60-12
Dahill, Jr., T.H.: 56-27
Dahl, George L.: ME-19
Dahn, Richard F.: 60-3
Dailey, Gardner A.: SD-8
Dailey, Merlin C.: 58-3
Dal, Harald: 57-40
Dale, Lola E.: 56-25
Dali, Salvador: 54-16, 58-15, 59-19, 62-8, 62-18, 62-28, 63-33,
Dallegret, Francois: 65-6
Daly, Judith White: 53-17
Daly, Norman: 52-1
Dalzotto, Eugene: 53-16, 56-26
Dambiermont, Mary: 61-1
Damianovich, Zulema: 60-3, 60-15
Daminai, Jorge: 60-17
Damora, Robert: 64-21
Daniel, Mann, Johnson & Mendenhall: 62-24
Daniell, Thomas: 62-12
Daniell, Thomas & William: 61-22
Danto, Arthur Coleman: 55-20, 58-3
Danzig, Jerry: 57-16
Daphnis, Nassos: 60-41, 64-30, ME-73
Daphnis-Avlon, Helen: 64-30
Daplan, Jerome: 54-18
Daraniyagala, Justin: 58-42
Darby, Henry F.: 58-14
Darie, Sandu: 56-28
Darley, Felix: 64-1
Darling, J.N. (Ding): 57-3
Darling & Webel: 62-33
Darriau, Jean Paul: 58-12, 60-42
Darrow, W.: ME-28
Dart, Edward D.: 64-11, 64-21
Dasburg, Andrew: 59-42
Datz, Abraham Mark: 55-3
Daubigny, Charles Francois: 63-17, 63-20, NY-11, MMA-54-4
Daumier, Honore: 53-7, 55-19, 56-16, 59-20, 61-2, 62-27, 63-17, 64-5, ME-29, MMA-54-2, NY-7&7b, NY-21
Davey, Randall: 53-5
David, Ismar: 58-16
David, Jacques-Louis: 55-24
Davidson, Bruce: 59-56, 63-8
Davidson, Morris: 55-3, 64-30
Davidson, Patricia: 58-32
Davidsson, Kristjan: 66-2
Davie, Alan: 57-27, 60-14, 61-4, 61-29, 64-2, NY-8
Davies, Arthur B.: 55-19, 57-11, 59-6, 60-13, 62-17, 64-3, 65-2, NY-19
Davies, Kenneth: 59-24
Davila, Alberto: 60-17
Davis: 54-25, NY-20
Davis, Alexander Jackson: 64-1
Davis, Charles H.: 62-7
Davis, Don: 58-39
Davis, Frederick W.: 61-30
Davis, J.H.: ME-11
Davis, John W.: 65-4
Davis, Joseph H.: 59-18, 64-1
Davis, Lenore: 58-32
Davis, Noel: 56-1
Davis, Paul: 64-25
Davis, Richard: 52-4
Davis, Stuart: 54-10, 55-9, 58-15, 59-6, 59-7, 59-31, 60-13, 60-27, 62-28, 64-30, ME-7, ME-10, ME-31, ME-55, NY-5
Davis, Brody & Wisniewski: 64-11, 64-21
Dawo, Thomsa & Ilse: 61-1
Day, Lucienne: 52-7
Day, Worden: 51-21, 56-25, 56-26, 57-32, 57-36, 58-3, 58-26, 58-42, 60-3, 60-24, 62-8, NY-3
de Allende, David: 54-42
De Balzac, H.: 58-36
De Beaumont, Etienne: 59-19
de Boullongne, Louise: 55-24
de Brocquy, Louis: 53-24
De Camp, Joseph Rodefer: 63-1
De Camps, Alexandre: 63-20
De Carava, Roy: 59-56
de Chavannes, Puvis: 62-5
de Chirico, Giorio: 55-18, 57-34, 59-19
De Concorezzo, Victor: 61-1
de Creeft, José: 55-12, 56-22, 57-15, 58-16, 59-14, 59-51, 62-16
de Diego, Julio: 53-5
de Faenza, Antonio Gentili: 61-22
De Forest, Roy: 59-24
De Gelder, D.: 51-3
De Gheyn: 54-11, 64-9
de Gorgoza, Patricia: 62-8
de Grave, Jean Jacques: 56-21
de Groot, Nanno: 64-30
de Hooghe, Romeyn: 59-40
De Kooning, Elaine: 55-19, 62-16, 64-26
De Kooning, Willem: 56-2, 59-23, 60-14, 61-29, 62-27, 64-2, ME-41, ME-55, ME-73, NY-18, NY-20
La Fresnaye, Roger de: 59-23, 61-24, 62-5, 63-31
De la Verriere, Jean Jacques: 62-10
De Laclotte, Hyacinthe: 62-2
De Lairesse, Gerard: 62-36
De Laittre, Eleanor: 55-3
De Lajoue, Jacques: 55-24, 59-40
De Lalonde, Richard: 59-40
De Laurentiis, Tonino: 61-1
De Long, David: 64-25
De Maar-Sielckem, Harriet: 61-1
De Marco, Jean: 52-4
De Maria, Dolores: 53-17, 57-14
De Martini, Joseph: 56-2, ME-73
De Maupassant, G.: 58-36
De Menocal, Richard: 64-3
De Modena, Nicoletto Rosex: 59-40
De Niro, Robert: 58-16, 60-22, 60-43, 64-26
De Patta, Margaret: 54-43
De Pinna, Vivian: 64-30
De Pisis, Filippo: 57-34, 58-23
De Poli, Paolo: 61-1
De Rivera, Jose: 55-12, 56-22, 58-41, 59-31, 60-32, ME-55
De Roos, S.H.: 61-20
De Rose, Anthony Lewis: 58-14
De Ruiter, Guus: 53-2
De Saussure, J.: 53-21
De Shaies, Arthur: ME-73
De Silva, y Velasquez Diego Rodriguez: 56-16
De Stael, Nicholas: 54-18, 55-23, 60-14, 62-28, ME-40
De Szyszlo, Fernando: 54-18, 60-17
De Tessan, (Suzanne) Froncoiz (Comtesse): 57-ee
De Tivoli, Serafino: 63-10
De Tramontana, Isabel: ME-75
De Vaserly, Victor: 61-4
De Vega, L.: 58-36
De Vita, Luciano: 61-11
De Vlaminck, Maurice: 58-34
De Vries, Han: 61-20
De Wailly, Charles: 59-40
De Wint, Peter: 62-12
De Witte, Pieter: 64-9
Dean, Donald R.: 62-10
Dean, Loomis: 58-A&B
Dearden, Francis: 53-17
Dearstyne, Howard: 63-2
Deas, Charles: 64-1, ME-11
DeBeck, Billy: 57-3
Debenjak, Riko: 56-15, 56-21
Decamps, Alexandre Gabrielle: 65-10
Deck, Francis: 53-25
Decker, Lindsey: 57-12, 60-22, 60-42, 63-29
Dee Leo J.: 65-11
Deese, Rupert: 51-15, 55-22
DeFrancesco, Ray: ME-75
Degas, Edgar: 55-24, 57-18, 60-14, 61-2, 63-14, ME-32, ME-55, MMA-54-2, NY-7 &7b
Degottex, Jean: 64-10
Dehn, Adolf: 53-2, 53-12, 54-18, 55-13, 56-1, 56-2, 60-1, ME-7, ME-73
Dehner, Dorothy: 56-25, 0-24, 60-42, 62-40, ME-56
DeJode: 63-19
Del Deo, Salvatore: 64-29, 64-30
Del Ghirlandajo, Domneico: 56-16
Del Sarto, Andrea: 64-9
Delacroix, Eugène: 55-24, 57-18, 62-20, 65-10, 67-19, ME-32, NY-21
Delafosse, Jean-Charles: 59-40
Delano, Jack: 64-28
Delaunay, Sonia: 55-19
Delevanti, S.: 56-2
Delfau, Andre: 59-19
Delhez, Victor: 54-16
Della, Francesca Piero: 56-16
Delmaet & Durandelle: 62-25
Delonga, Leonard: ME-75
DeLorme, William: 53-26
Delpierre, Francine: 61-1
Deluigi, Mario: 61-16
Delvaux, Paul: 60-4
DeMolas, Nicolas: 59-19
Demuth, Charles: 55-15, 55-19, 58-34, 60-13, 60-27, 63-14, 64-4, 64-30, 65-2, ME-7, ME-23, ME-27, ME-31, ME-32, ME-40, ME-41, NY-5, NY-20
Denis Maurice: 54-16, 62-5, 62-45
Dennis Warren: 57-31, 61-35
Denst, Jack: 64-23
Dente, Marco: 62-18
DePaoli, Carly: 54-8
DePatta, Margaret: 57-6, 60-5
DePauw, Victor: 56-2
DePian: 63-19
Derain, Andre: 57-30, 59-19, 62-5, 62-29, 63-14
Der Harootian, Koren: 52-4
DeRocchi, Francisco: 51-18
Deroy: ME-29
Derujinsky, Gleb W.: ME-75
Derval, Jean: 61-1
Deshaies, Arthur: 55-20, 56-26, 56-27, 60-3, 60-22, NE-96, NY-3
Designs for Business, Inc.: 61-30
Deskey, Donald: 61-30
Desnoyer, Francois: 60-15, NE-96
Despiau, Charles: 63-31
Desprez, Jean Louis: 61-22, 62-20
Destefano, Armando: 58-40
Detre, Roland: 56-2
DeVitis, Themis: 56-2
Dewing, Maria Oakey: 62-7
Dewing, Thomas Wilmer: 62-7, 62-17, 63-1, 64-3
Dey, Andrew & Muriel: 58-16, 60-5
Deyrolle, Jean: 64-10
Dhaemers, Margaret: 60-12
Dhaemers, Robert A.: 58-7
Dhir, Lily Shufff: 55-20
Dhner, Dorothy: 58-3
Di Buoninsegna, Duccio: 56-16
Di Gesu, Antony: 62-45
Di Martini, Joseph: 55-19
Di Prete, Danilo: 60-17
Di Suvero, Mark: 64-20
Di Vincenzo, Bernardo Sozi: 59-40
Diaz, de la Pena Virgilio Narcisso: 63-20, MMA-54-4
Dibdin, T.C.: 62-12
Dickinson, Edwin Walter: 54-25, 62-38, 64-3, 64-29, 64-30, 65-11, NY-11, NY-18
Dickinson, Preston: 58-34, 60-13, 61-25, ME-31
Dickson, Helen: 56-27
Didyk, Ann: 53-5
Diebenkorn, Richard: 55-2, 56-2, 58-7, 60-43, 64-2, ME-33, ME-42, ME-60, ME-73, NY-18
Diederen, Jef: 61-4
Diehl, Gottried: 54-18, NE-96
Dienes, Sari: 53-16, 59-14, 60-24, 62-8, 63-24, 63-29
Dietz, Albert: 58-28
Dieuzaide, J.: 62-45
DiFranza, Emilio A.: 56-27
Dikkenboer, Daniel Den: 56-15
Dikmen, Oktay: 56-21
Diller, Burgoyne: 60-41, ME-73
Dimondstein, Morton: 55-5
Dine, Jim: 62-41, 65-11
Dinnerstein, Harvey: 55-5
Dirks, Rudolph: 57-3
Disberg, Harry: 56-21
Disderi, Adolphe-Eugene: 56-5
Dittmer, Robert P.: 58-32
Dix, Otto: 54-16, 54-18, 56-7, 58-35, 59-36
Dobashi, Jun: 58-42
Dobbertin, Eugene F.: 52-7
Dobbs, John: 58-40
Dobin, Fred: 56-2
Dobkin, Alex: 57-10
Dodd, Lamar: 53-5, 53-12, 61-26, 64-31, ME-73
Dodd, Robert: 62-15
Dodson, William: MMA-54-2
Doebele, H.P.: 53-2
Dole, William: 62-31
Dolenoord, Jenny: 51-3
Domareki, Joseph: ME-73
Domela, Cesar: 64-10
Dominis, John: 58-A&B
Domjan, Joseph: 60-3, 60-15
Domoto, Hiaso: 61-4
Donald, Barthelme & Associates: ME-19
Donati, Enrico: 57-1, 58-43, 59-10, 59-23, 60-27, ME-73
Donato, Louis: 56-2
Donelli, Antonio: 58-9
Donelly, C.P.: ME-19
Doney, T.: ME-29
Dong, Wing C.: 53-16
Donghi, Antonio: 51-18
Dooijes, Dick: 61-20
Dooley, Mary Lou: 58-3
Doolittle, Amos: ME-29
Dorazio, Piero: 59-35, 60-20
Dorazi,o Ralph: 55-20
Dorfsman, Lou: 60-37
Dorgan, (Tad) T.A.: 57-3
Doughty, Thomas: 60-28, 65-2, ME-7, NY-4
Dova, Gianni: 58-23, 60-15
Dove, Arthur Garfield: 53-9, 54-25, 55-11, 55-15, 55-16, 59-6, 60-13, 60-27, 62-27, ME-7, ME-31
Dowing, Joseph: 60-15
Dowling, Dan: 57-3
Downs, Allen: 62-45
Downs, Phyllis: 58-6
Downs, Robert: 58-39
Dozier, Otis: 57-23
Dozier, Velma: 57-6
Drabkin, Stella: ME-7
Dragomir, Jean Claude: 57-27
Dreisbach, David: 55-6
Drentwelt, Abraham: 55-24
Drerup, Karl: 57-6
Drerup & Salo Karl & George K.: 58-16
Drewes, Werner: 56-2, 58-3, 60-3, ME-7
Drexler, Rosalyn: NY-17, NY-18
Driesbach, David F.: 60-3
Driggs, Elsie: 56-2, 64-30
Droste, Karl-Heinz: 61-4, 64-14
Drumlevitch, Seymour: 55-2, 55-9, 57-1, 61-15, NY-10
Drumm, Donald: 65-6
Drummond, Sally Hazelett: 62-37
Du Bois, Guy Pène: 63-15, 64-3
Du Bois, Raoul Pene: 59-19
Du Camp, Maxime: NY-1
Du Cerceau, Jacques Adrouet (Elder): 59-40
Du Pen, Everett: 65-3
Duak, Fatme: 56-29
Dubar, George: 55-6
Dubin, Ralph: 57-2
Duble, Lu: 52-4
DuBose, Charles: 65-3
Dubuffet, Jean: 59-23, 60-4, 60-14, 60-15, 61-4, 62-41, 64-2, ME-46, NY-18
Duca Alfred: 59-6
DuCasse, Ralph: 58-7
Duchamp, Marcel: 59-14
Duchamp-Villon, Raymond: 61-24
Duck, Jacob: 63-17
Duderstadt, Bruce: 62-10
Duell, Howard D.: 58-32
Duffy, Edmund: 57-3
Dufy, Raoul: 57-9, 57-30, 61-33, 62-5, 63-14, ME-55
Dulac, Malvin: 56-27
Dullanty, Patrick: 56-25
Dumouchel, Albert: 59-3, 61-4
Duncan, David Douglas: 56-5, 58-A&B, 59-17, 59-56
Duncan, Florida: 64-30
Duncan, John R.: 62-3
Duncan, Jr., George R.: 53-24
Dunkel, William (Dr.): 53-21
Dunn, Alan: 55-13, ME-28
Dunn, John: 55-22, 64-28
Dupre, Jules: 63-20, MMA-54-4
Duquette, Tony: 59-19
Durand, Asher Brown: 58-14, 60-28, 64-1, ME-11, NY-4
Durand, John: 62-2
Durchanek, Ludvik: 60-12, 64-25, ME-75
Durer, Albrecht: 55-10, 56-16, 57-18, 57-37, 62-18, 63-4, 63-17, 64-9, 64-19, ME-65, NY-9, NY-21
Durfee, Hazard: 52-11
Durham, I.D.: 61-35
Durkee, Steve: 63-7
Durrie, George Henry: 60-28, NY-4
Duryea & Elkins: ME-19
Dusart, Cornelis: 60-40
Dusenberry, W.C.: NY-13
Duval, Sally W.: ME-75
Duveneck, Frank: 59-34, 62-7, ME-11
Duver, Albrecht: NY-9
Duvigneaud, Diane: 55-5
Duvoisin, Roger: 61-33
Duynen, Isaac van: MMA-54-3
Dworzan, George: ME-75
Dzubas, Friedebald: 51-21
Eades, Luis: 57-23, NY-10
Eakins, Thomas: 54-25, 55-19, 58-27, 59-6, 59-24, 59-34, 60-13, 62-17, 62-28, 63-3, ME-7, ME-11 ME-31, ME-32, ME-41, ME-55
Eames, Charles: 55-22
Earl, Ralph: 54-25, 60-13, 62-2, 62-17, 63-15, ME-31
Easterwood, Henry: ME-75
Eastman, Seth: 61-3, 64-1
Eaton, Wyatt: 62-7
Eaves, John: 54-18
Ebendorf, Robert: ME-75
Ebert, Charles: 64-31
Eby, Kerr: ME-7
Echave, Jose: 60-17
Eckels, Robert J.: 60-5
Eckerberg, Margareta: 57-14
Eckhardt, Barbara: 55-5
Eckhardt, Edris: ME-75
Economous, Michael: 62-3
Edmonds, Francis William: 58-27
Edmondson, Leonard: 53-12, 55-20, 56-26, 58-3, 58-7, 60-3, 62-3, ME-73, NY-3
Edmonstone, Robert: 65-10
Edwards, Estor Elsie: 57-14
Edwards, Ethel: 53-12, 64-30
Edwards, George W.: ME-19
Edwards, Joel: 57-6
Edwards, Stanley D.: 65-4
Eeckhout: 54-11
Eero Saarinen & Assoc: 63-16, 65-9
Egas, Camilo: 62-16
Egbert, Lyn: 60-5
Egeler, Ernst: 53-21
Egert, Thalia: 53-24
Ehrenreich, Emma: 58-3, 64-30
Eichenberg, Fritz: 54-16
Eichholz, Duane: 57-14
Eichler (the Younger), Johann Gottried: 59-40
Eiermann, Egon: 58-28
Eights, James: NY-15
Eikaas, Ludvig: 54-18, 57-40
Eilshemius, Louis M.: 59-31, 60-27, 61-25, 61-27, 62-1, 62-28, 64-3, ME-74, NY-5
Einsel, Walter: 60-37
Einsenstadt, Alfred: 56-5, 59-56, 58-A&B
Eisner, Anne: 55-3
Eisner, Dorothy: 55-3
Ekstrom, Thea: 62-44
El Greco: 56-16, 57-18, NY-7&7b
Elder, Eldon: 62-14, 64-35
Eldred, Dale: 59-12, 65-7
Eldrege, Mary: ME-75
Eldridge, Henry: 62-12
Elenbaas, V.H.: 56-15
Elenbaas, Wally: 51-3, 53-2, 61-20
Elffers, Dick: 61-20
Elgart, Eliot: 51-1, 53-5
Elias, Arthur: 54-27
Elias, Harold: 55-5
Eliasoph, Paula: 55-3
Eliezer, R.: 58-36
Eliot, Noyes & Associates: 65-9
Elisofon Eliot: 58-A&B, 59-56
Ellenzweig, Harry: 62-31